artboost.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy of artboost.com | Help Center | Artboost

**Last updated:** 23\. May, 2018

Artboost ApS (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website [https://artboost.com](https://artboost.com/) including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”). 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.   
**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE SITE.  **

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Revised” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification. You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.   

Artboost ApS, Denmark, Njalsgade 19D, 1st fl., 2300 Copenhagen

We may collect information about you in a variety of ways. The information we may collect on the Site includes: 

#### Personal Data 

Personally identifiable information, such as your name, shipping address, email address, and telephone number, and demographic information, such as your age, gender, hometown, and interests, that you voluntarily give to us when you register with the Site or when you choose to participate in various activities related to the Site, such as online chat and message boards. You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Site. 

#### Derivative Data 

Information our servers automatically collect when you access the Site, such as your IP address, your browser type, your operating system, your access times, and the pages you have viewed directly before and after accessing the Site.

#### Financial Data 

Financial information, such as data related to your payment method (e.g. valid credit card number, card brand, expiration date) that we may collect when you purchase, order, return, exchange, or request information about our services from the Site. We store only very limited, if any, financial information that we collect. Otherwise, all financial information is stored by our payment processor, Stripe, and you are encourage review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. 

#### Facebook Permissions 

The  Site  may  by  default  access  your  Facebook basic  account  information, including  your  name,  email,  gender,  birthday,  current  city,  and  profile  picture URL, as well as other information that you choose to make public. We may also request access to other permissions related to your account, such as friends, checkins, and likes, and you may choose to grant or deny us access to each individual permission.  For  more  information regarding  Facebook  permissions, refer to the Facebook Permissions Reference page.

This Application may ask for some Facebook permissions allowing it to perform actions with the User’s Facebook account and to retrieve information, including Personal Data, from it.

For more information about the following permissions, refer to the [Facebook permissions documentation](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/authentication/permissions/) and to the [Facebook privacy policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

The permissions asked are the following:

**Basic information**

By default, this includes certain User’s Data such as id, name, picture, gender, and their locale. Certain connections of the User, such as the Friends, are also available. If the user has made more of their data public, more information will be available.

**Access Friend Lists**

Provides access to any friend lists the user created in order to help you as a user to connect with the people you know.

**Email**

Provides access to the user’s primary email address

#### Data From Social Networks 

User information from social networking sites, such as Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest, Twitter, including your name, your social network username, location, gender, birth date, email address, profile picture, and public data for contacts, if you connect your account to such social networks. 

#### Data From Contests, Giveaways, and Surveys 

Personal and other information you may provide when entering contests or giveaways and/or responding to surveys.

#### Other Personal Data 

Other data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.  
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.

Users are responsible for any Personal Data of third parties obtained, published or shared through this Application and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.

Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a smooth, efficient,  and  customised  experience.  Specifically,  we  may  use  information collected about you via the Site to:

  * Administer sweepstakes, promotions, and contests.
  * Compile anonymous statistical data and analysis for use internally or with third parties. 
  * Create and manage your account. 
  * Deliver  targeted  advertising,  coupons,  newsletters,  and  promotions,  and other information regarding our website and mobile application to you. 
  * Email you regarding your account or order. 
  * Enable user-­to-­user communications. 
  * Fulfil and manage purchases, orders, payments, and other transactions related to the Site. 
  * Generate  a  personal  profile  about  you  to  make  future  visits  to  the  Site more personalised. 
  * Increase the efficiency and operation of the Site. 
  * Monitor and analyse usage and trends to improve  your experience with the Site. 
  * Notify you of updates to the Site. 
  * Offer new products, services, and/or recommendations to you. 
  * Perform other business activities as needed. 
  * Process payments and refunds.
  * Request feedback and contact you about your use of the Site. 
  * Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems. 
  * Respond to product and customer service requests. 
  * Send you a newsletter. 
  * Solicit support for the Site.

We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows: 

#### By Law or to Protect Rights 

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### Third­Party Service Providers  

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance.

#### Marketing Communications 

With your consent, or with an opportunity for you to withdraw consent, we may share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.  

#### Interactions with Other Users 

If you interact with other users of the Site, those users may see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity, including sending invitations to other users, chatting with other users, liking posts, following blogs. 

#### Online Postings 

When you post comments, contributions or other content to the Site, your posts may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside the Site in perpetuity. 

#### Affiliates 

We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.

#### Business Partners 

We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions. 

#### Social Media Contacts  

If you connect to the Site through a social network, your contacts on the social network will see your name, profile photo, and descriptions of your activity. 

#### Other Third Parties 

We may share your information with advertisers and investors for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. We may also share your information with such third parties for marketing purposes, as permitted by law.  

#### Sale or Bankruptcy 

If we reorganise or sell all or a portion of our assets, undergo a merger, or are acquired by another entity, we may transfer your information to the successor entity. If we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, your information would be an asset transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that the transferee may decline honor commitments we made in this Privacy Policy. 

We are not responsible for the actions of third parties with whom you share personal or sensitive data, and we have no authority to manage or control thirdparty solicitations. If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly

#### Cookies and Web Beacons 

We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on the Site to help customise the Site and improve your experience. For more information on how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy posted on the Site, which is incorporated into this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by our 

#### Website Analytics  

We may also partner with selected third-­party vendors, such as Google Analytics, Mixpanel, to allow tracking technologies and remarketing services on the Site through the use of first party cookies and third-­party cookies, to, among other things, analyse and track users’ use of the Site, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity. By accessing the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by these third­-party vendors. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly for responses to your questions. We do not transfer personal information to these third­-party vendors. However, If you do not want any information to be collected and used by tracking technologies, you can visit the third-­party vendor or Network Advertising Initiative Opt­Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt­Out Tool. You should be aware that getting a new computer, installing a new browser, upgrading an existing browser, or erasing or otherwise altering your browser’s cookies files may also clear certain opt-­out cookies, plug­ins, or settings.

The Site may contain links to third-­party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to any third-­party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site. 

We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorised parties. Therefore, we cannot guarantee complete security if you provide personal information. 

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 13. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 13, please contact us using the contact information provided below. 

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do­NotTrack (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognising and implementing DNT signals has been finalised. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.

#### Methods of processing

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do­NotTrack (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognising and implementing DNT signals has been finalised. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.

#### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.

#### Retention time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Access to third party services’ accounts, Analytics and Managing contacts and sending messages.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services: 

#### Access to third party services’ accounts

These services allow this Application to access Data from your account on a third party service and perform actions with it.

These services are not activated automatically, but require explicit authorization by the User. 

#### Access to the Facebook account (This Application)

This service allows this Application to connect with the User’s account on the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc.

Permissions asked: Access Friend Lists and Email.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

#### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

**Google Analytics (Google)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

**Google Tag Manager (Google)**

Google Tag Manager is an analytics service provided by Google, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage data.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

These services make it possible to manage a database of email contacts, phone contacts or any other contact information to communicate with the User.

These services may also collect data concerning the date and time when the message was viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacted with it, such as by clicking on links included in the message.

#### Mailchimp (Mailchimp)

Mailchimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by Mailchimp Inc.

Personal Data collected: Email address.

Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

#### Legal action

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.  
The User declares to be aware that the Data Controller may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.

#### Additional information about User’s Personal Data

In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

#### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

#### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the end of this document.

#### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

#### Account Information 

You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by: 

  * Logging into user account settings and updating the user account. 

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller removes the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-­out by: 

  * Noting your preferences at the time you register your account with the Site.
  * Logging into your account settings and updating your preferences. 
  * Contacting us using the contact information provided. 

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Artboost ApS  
Njalsgade 19D, st fl  
2300 Copenhagen S  
Denmark

Phone: +45 2567 6624  
Email: help[@artboost.com](mailto:help@artboost.com)
